Oh, man!
이런 맙소사!
-What's that?
-Treeger's snaking the shower drain.
뭐야
트리거 씨가 하수구 뚫고 있어
What in the name of hell?
사람 환장하겠네
Maybe he found your flip-flop.
네 슬리퍼 나왔나보다
어라?
워우! 저거 포르노냐?
Is this porn?
I must have hit something
on the remote.
내가 방금 뭘 눌렀지?
Do we pay for this?
우리 돈 냈냐?
We didn't even pay our cable bill.
케이블 요금도 안 냈어
Maybe this is how they punish us.
이게 징계조치인가 봐
Maybe we shouldn't pay our phone bill.
Free phone sex.
전화요금도 안 냈으면
폰섹스도 공짜일 텐데
Maybe we shouldn't pay our gas bill.
가스요금도 내지 말자
Hey, that lady's all kinds of naked.
저런, 확실히 벗겨놨네
Joey pressed something on the remote
and it just came on.
조이가 리모콘에서 뭘 눌렀더니
그냥 나오지 뭐예요
나도 그런 적 있어
채널을 돌리다가 짠!
It happened to me once.
It was like finding money.
노다지 캔 거지
Finding money
with naked people on it!
노다지도 캐고 알몸도 보고
그러다 무심코 TV를 껐는데
다신 안 나오더라구
But I made the mistake
of turning off the TV.
I never got it back again.
아직도 속이 쓰려
And I'm sad.
Why would he turn off the TV?
그걸 왜 꺼?
The One with the Free Porn
Do we really have to watch this
while we eat?
못살아, 밥 먹는데
이걸 꼭 봐야겠니?
안돼! 안돼! 안돼!
잘못하면 안 나올지도 몰라
We don't know
what could make this go away.
So no one touches the remote,
and no one touches the TV.
아무도 리모콘 건드리지 마
TV도 손대지 말고
And no one touches the air
around the TV.
TV 근처에 얼씬도 하지 마
Imagine a protective porn bubble,
if you will.
포르노 방어막이
작동 중이라고 생각해
I'm at least going to mute it.
- 그럼 소리라도 죽여
- 아서! 아서! 아서!
We still have porn.
- 아직 살아있어
- 그래
- 나야
- 안녕
그런 걸 들면 어떡해
이리 줘
What are you doing?
That's too heavy. Give it here.
- 고마워
- 되게 무겁네...
Oh, God.
알았다
I'm too pregnant for lugging
around a stupid massage table.
마사지 테이블 끌고 다니기엔
몸이 너무 무거워
좀더 작은 테이블로
할 수 있는 일은 없을까?
I need a job with a smaller table.
Or a job without a table.
- 테이블이 필요 없는 일은 어때
- 의사 같은 거?
You mean, like a doctor?
You're blocking the porn!
포르노 가리잖아, 비켜
저런...
That reminds me.
I have to see my ob-gyn today.
이거 보니까 오늘
병원 갈 일이 생각나네
- 나야
- 그래
Emily just went to the airport.
에밀리는 방금 공항으로 떠났어
Why didn't you take her?
바래다주지 그랬어
Her uncle had planned to do it.
삼촌이 나오기로 하셨대
아침에 작별 인사했어
We said our goodbyes this morning.
많이 서운하겠다
참, 앞집에 공짜 포르노 나와
You must feel horrible.
Hey, the guys have free porn.
싫어, 에이...
Hey, cheer up.
You'll see her again, right?
어깨 좀 펴
다시 만날 텐데 뭐
나도 그걸 잘 모르겠어
I don't know.
When I brought it up, she said...
그 얘기만 나오면 에밀리는...
..."This is so fantastic.
Why talk about the future?
'지금이 좋잖아, 왜 앞날을
걱정해? 이 순간을 즐겨... '
-Let's enjoy"
-Don't do the accent. It really bums me out.
그 말투 흉내 내지 마
닭살 돋아
Emily said I was pretty good.
에밀리는 그럴 듯하다던데?
Well, that's someone
you should hang on to.
그야 접대용 멘트고
You've got to see her again.
꼭 다시 만나야 돼
-Why do you care?
-Because!
- 왜 그렇게 신경 쓰는데?
- 그야...
You could live out my fantasy.
이건 내 환상이니까
You had fantasies about Emily?
에밀리한테 환상을 품었니?
You know, the fantasy.
아니, 오빠도 알잖아
내 환상...
Meet a foreigner, fall madly in love
and spend your lives together.
낯선 땅에서 온 이방인과 뜨거운
사랑에 빠져 함께 여생을 보낸다
Is that why you hung out
with that Ukrainian kid in school?
중학교 때 우크라이나 애랑
어울린 게 그 때문이었어?
Yeah, plus his mom used to put
sour cream on everything.
맞아, 또 걔네 엄마는 어디에나
사워크림을 듬뿍 얹어주거든
Do you love her?
에밀리를 사랑해?
We said it would only be two weeks.
어차피 2주가 전부였어
사랑하는구나
You love her.
What is love, really?
사랑이 도대체 뭔데
I knew you loved her!
사랑하는 줄 알았어
You go to the airport and tell her.
공항으로 가서 고백해
You'll probably catch her at the gate.
게이트로 들어가고 있을 거야
You'll call her name
and yell "l love you!"
이름을 크게 부르고
사랑한다고 외쳐
She'll say "l love you too!"
그럼 에밀리도
사랑한다고 하겠지
Then you will have
the most amazing kiss.
그리고 이어지는
열렬한 키스
Everyone at the gate will applaud.
주위에서 박수가 터질 거야
I am a good kisser.
내가 키스는 잘하지
Then you two can sneak
into the cockpit.
그런 다음 조종실에
몰래 숨어 들어가서...
Things will start to heat up.
분위기가 달아오르자...
And then a stewardess comes in....
스튜어디스가 들어오고...
I've been watching too much porn.
포르노 그만 봐야겠다
-ls that the heartbeat?
-That's it.
- 이게 심장소리예요?
- 그래요
어머, 세상에!
Oh, my God!
정말 신기하다
This is so cool!
Have we talked about multiple births?
하나가 아닐 수도 있다는
말씀 드렸던가요?
Let's take care of this one. If l
get pregnant again, I have your card.
우선 얘 한 명만 봐주시고
또 임신하면 꼭 찾아올게요
No, I'm getting
three separate heartbeats.
그게 아니라
심장소리가 세 개예요
You guys were worried
I wouldn't even have one.
세 개나? 하나도
장담 못한다면서요
Doctors are wrong all the time.
- 의사 말 맞는 거 봤어요?
- 하긴...
Are you sure that there are three?
정말 셋이에요?
-Definitely.
-Oh, my God.
- 확실해요
- 맙소사
세상에
엄마야!
So in a few months, I'll have three
babies walking around inside me?
몇 달 후면 애들이 셋씩이나
내 뱃속에서 뛰어다니나요?
It'll be like one of those log rides
when they come shooting out.
그럼 통나무 탈 때처럼
일렬종대로 발사되겠네?
Giving birth to three
is like giving birth to one.
사실 셋이나 하나나
낳을 땐 비슷해요
What do you know?
잘도 아시네!
-Have you ever had triplets?
-No. I'm sorry, I haven't.
세쌍둥이 낳아보셨어요?
- 아쉽게도 그런 적은 없군요
- 이것도 큰 벼슬이다
I'm going to use this a lot.
오, 피비
- 어서 와요
- 잘 있었어요?
How'd it go at the doctor's?
병원에서 뭐래요?
그니까 우리가 길을 걷다가
You know how, when you're
walking down the street...
세 사람이 나란히 서있으면
'와, 근사하다' 그러잖아?
...and you see three people in a row.
And you say "Oh, that's nice."
- 맞아!
- 그래
좋은 소식이야
세쌍둥이래, 악!
Good news!
You'll have three babies.
세쌍둥이요?
Three babies?
드디어 내 밴드 생겼다!
I've finally got my band!
늘 식구가 많았으면 했는데
We'll have a big family!
I always wanted a big family.
두 사람이 기뻐해서 다행이다
당황하면 어쩌나 걱정했거든
Oh, God, I'm so glad you're happy!
I was afraid you'd be freaked.
왜 당황해?
Why would we be freaked?
키우기도 힘들고
돈도 많이 들잖아
Because it's harder to raise them
and the added expense.
아...
Right.
그렇군요
No, back to happy.
Back to happy!
안돼, 다시 아까처럼 기뻐해
아뇨, 문제없어요
왜냐면...
It's going to be fine...
...because I teach home ec.
내가 가정학을 가르치니까
학생들 30명한테 1년 내내
아기 옷만 만들라고 하죠 뭐
I can have 30 kids making
baby clothes all year long.
It'll be like my very own
little sweatshop.
무임금에 노동력
착취가 되겠지만
I was thinking, ever since
you said we'd have triplets.
세쌍둥이라는 말 듣고
그간 고민 많이 했는데
아무래도 학교 그만두고
취직하는 게 좋겠어
The best thing for me to do is
drop out of college and get a job.
- 안돼, 프랭크
- 학교를 그만두다니, 안돼
No, you can't quit college.
You're in college?
근데 너 학교 다니니?
Refrigerator college.
- 냉장학 전문대
- 네
이제 곧 아빠가 될 거니까
제대로 된 직업이 있어야지
When we found out
we were having a baby...
...I figured I should have
a career, you know?
난 냉장고도 무지 좋아해
And I love refrigerators.
You can't give up on your dream!
꿈을 포기해선 안돼
No, it's okay.
We're going to have three kids.
아냐, 괜찮아
아이가 셋이나 생기잖아
And that's a different kind of dream.
그건 또 다른 내 꿈이야
Three kids and no money.
세 아기와 알거지
This is the boarding call
for flight 009.
009편의 탑승이 시작됐습니다
에밀리!
세상에, 웬일이야?
What are you doing here?
I had to see you
before you took off.
떠나기 전에
한 번 더 보고 싶었어
You are so sweet.
사랑스러운 사람
캔디바 엄청 크다
That's a big candy bar.
I had the most amazing time with you.
정말 꿈같은 시간이었어
Me too.
나도
This is the final boarding call
for flight 009.
009편의 마지막
탑승안내방송입니다
Well, that's me.
들어가야겠어
Here, have this.
이거 받아, 어차피 기내에는
짐 하나밖에 못 들고 가잖아
I'm only allowed
one piece of carry-on.
잠깐만
Listen, I have to tell you something.
잘 들어, 자기한테
할말이 있어
I've been thinking.
쭉 생각해왔는데...
I'm just going to say it, okay?
그냥 말해버릴게
나 있지...
I think...
...I love you.
자기를 사랑해
Thank you.
고마워
It's no problem.
별말씀을
What is that song?
이게 무슨 노래지?
종일 입에서 맴도는데
It's the theme
from Good Will Humping.
'굿 윌 험핑' 주제가야
You know who doesn't like
dirty movies? My boyfriend Joshua.
내 남자친구 조슈아는
그런 지저분한 영화 질색이야
Yeah, right.
알아 모시죠
내가 들었어, 상상에
맡기는 편이 더 좋대
He said he prefers to leave
certain things to the imagination.
유치하기 짝이 없는 대사에
볼 것도 없고 웃음만 나온다지?
Did he also say that
the dialogue was corny?
-And that he found it funny, not sexy?
-Yes.
맞아
Yeah, he likes porn.
포르노 좋아하네
Where you going?
어디 가?
To find out if he really
thinks models are too skinny.
슈퍼모델들도 비쩍 말라서
볼품없다고 했거든
왔니?
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
How'd it go?
프랭크하고 앨리스는?
Frank has to quit college...
슈퍼 임산부 누나 덕분에
내 동생 자퇴하게 생겼다
...because his super-fertile
sister's having three babies.
I need to make money fast.
I wanted to talk to you about an idea.
당장 큰 돈을 벌어야 하는데
너랑 그 얘기 좀 하려고
You work for a big company.
큰 회사에 다니잖아
내부자 거래는 어때
Insider trading.
나한테 줄 만한 정보 있어?
What information can you give me?
They don't talk to us
about that stuff.
그런 얘기는 내가 못 듣고
수정액은 갖다 줄 수 있어
But I can get you free White-Out.
-Did you do what I said?
-I did.
- 내가 시킨 대로 말했어?
- 했지
-What'd she say?
-"Thank you."
- 그래서 뭐래?
- 고마워
You're totally welcome.
What'd she say?
별말씀을!
뭐라고 했어?
She said, "Thank you."
고맙다고 했다니까
I said, "l love you."
난 사랑한다고 했는데
에밀리 왈... '고마워'
And she said, "Thank you."
That's not right.
이게 아닌데
잠깐, 사랑한다고 했어?
Did you say you love her?
어쩌자고 일을 저질러
What were you trying
to get her to do?
-What do I do now?
-You play hard-to-get.
- 이제 어떡하지?
- 잠시 거리를 둬
She already lives in London.
안 그래도 런던에 살아
So you go to Tokyo.
그럼 넌 도쿄로 가라
Forget it.
정리해, 깨끗이 잊어
고백했으면 끝난 거야
You told her you love her.
It's over.
It is not over!
You're over!
끝나지 않았어
끝난 건 너야
What?
뭐?
You know.
알잖아
좋아
Good one.
예리했어
It's not over. She'll call
and tell you she loves you.
곧 전화해서 오빠를
사랑한다고 할 거야
자기 감정이 두려워서
말을 못한 것뿐이지
Her feelings were so strong
that it scared her.
Go home and wait for her call.
She could call from the plane.
집에 가서 전화 기다려
비행기에서 전화할 거야
- 자, 어서 가
- 알았어
But if she doesn't call,
it is definitely over!
하지만 전화 안 하면
진짜 끝장이야
Unless, eventually, I call her
to see what's going on...
아냐, 내가 전화를 하지
뭐 안부도 물을 겸...
그 뒤에도 다시
전화를 안 해주면
...and she says she'll call me back,
but then she doesn't.
Then it's over!
그땐 정말 쫑낸다
Way to be strong!
대차게 나가라
- 어서 와
- 안녕
Can we watch cartoons on your TV?
여기서 만화 좀 봐도 되지?
포르노도 쉬엄쉬엄 봐야겠다
We need a porn break.
We spent two hours watching
In and Out and In Again.
두 시간 동안 '넣고 빼고
또 넣고'를 시청했거든
Why don't you turn it off?
그냥 꺼버리면 되잖아
Then we'd be the guys
who turned off free porn.
공짜 포르노채널을
끄는 게 인간이냐?
Yeah, but that's not
what you'd go by.
그런 생활신조가 있었어?
Look, I'm going
to have a kid someday. Okay?
나도 언젠가 아빠가 될 텐데
And someday that kid is going to ask me
if I ever turned off free porn.
애들이 공짜 포르노채널
껐냐고 물어보면 어떡해
그랬다고 말할 수는 없어
I don't wanna have to tell him that I did.
Did you ever asked you dad that?
너희 아빠한테도
그거 물어봤니?
I don't want to talk about it.
그런 얘기하기 싫어
Good, you're here!
다들 여기 있었구나
- 어서 와
- 안녕
그게 뭐야?
What you got there?
This? I'm glad you asked.
이거? 잘 물어봤어
Don't you hate to cut a tin can
with an ordinary steak knife?
평범한 스테이크나이프로
캔을 자를 때 짜증나시죠?
I know what you're thinking.
무슨 생각하는지 알아
Pregnant woman slays four?
살인마 임산부?
-Did they make you pay for those knives?
-No.
- 돈 주고 산 칼은 아니겠지?
- 아냐
-Are you sure?
-No.
- 확실해?
- 아니
You won't make enough money
by selling knives.
칼 팔아서는 동생네 돕기 힘들어
I just need enough money
for the second part of my plan.
그건 나도 알아, 2단계
사업자금만 모으면 돼
-What's that?
-My Saturn dealership.
- 2단계 사업이 뭔데
- 새턴 자동차대리점
Hello.
여보세요?
-Ross.
-Emily. Hi.
로스
에밀리, 안녕
여행은 어땠어?
How was your flight?
It was dreadful.
너무 끔찍했어
It was terrible how I acted
when you said those wonderful things.
자기 말 듣고 그렇게 와버려서
얼마나 미안했는지 몰라
No, that's all right.
아냐, 괜찮아
I'm just glad you called.
전화해줘서 고마워
Ross, there's something
that I've got to tell you.
로스, 실은 나
고백할 거 있어
다른 남자가 있어
There's someone else.
Does that mean the same thing
in England as it does in America?
그 표현은 영국이나
미국이나 같은 뜻이겠지?
She doesn't know who she wants.
Me or this "Colin" guy.
컬린이란 친구와 나 사이에서
갈등하는 것 같아
So I told her when she figures it out,
give me a call. Maybe I'll still be around.
결정되면 연락하라고 했어
내가 기다릴지 모르니까
When you say "still around," you mean still
around like you might be in a relationship...
그건 짐작이 간다
네가 기다린다고 할 땐
상대를 못 잊었거나 전화통
옆에서 죽어간다는 뜻이지
...or still around like you might have died
waiting for the phone to ring?
이렇게 되면 곤란한데
다른 남자가 있으면 안돼
But it was so right.
This isn't how it's supposed to go.
There can't be another guy.
난들 아니
Of course, there's another guy!
아냐, 다른 남자가 있어야지
This is even more perfect.
이건 더 완벽해
You have to prove your love!
이제 오빠의 사랑을 증명해
I'm not proving anything.
I'm done listening to you.
증명 같은 거 하기 싫어
다신 네 말 안 들어, 처음부터
공항에 가라는 말 안 들었으면
If I hadn't let you talk me
into this...
...I wouldn't have put my fist
through the wall.
주먹으로 벽 뚫는 일은 없었어
You did that?
- 주먹으로 벽을 뚫었어?
- 빗나가서 문을 쳤어
I missed and hit the door.
But it opened really hard.
엄청 세게 열리더라
You have to go to London.
You have to go fight for her.
- 런던으로 가
- 뭐?
- 싸워서 쟁취하는 거야
- 그래, 일리가 있다
That makes sense.
You said you loved her,
and she didn't say it back.
넌 사랑한다고 했는데
상대는 반응이 없었어
Then she told you about another guy.
Go to London. Scare her!
전화해서 다른 남자
있다는 얘기나 하고
너 런던에 가면
겁 좀 먹을 거다
When Rachel was with Paolo,
what did you do?
레이첼이 파올로랑 사귈 때
오빠 어떻게 했어?
I made fun of his accent.
그 녀석 말투를 흉내 냈지
가만히 앉아서 뺏겼잖아
싸울 생각도 안 했지?
You sat back and let him have her.
You didn't fight.
I just told you,
I made fun of him behind his back.
녀석 뒤통수에 대고
놀렸다니까
Oh, I see.
알았다
-You want that to happen with Emily?
-No.
- 에밀리도 그렇게 보낼 거야?
- 아니
All right then, go fight for her!
그럼 가서 싸워! 워우...
젠장, 완전히 뱀 소굴이네
It's like a snake pit.
That could be you and Emily.
오빠랑 에밀리도
저렇게 될 수 있어
That but nicer.
물론 훨씬 고상하겠지만
Go to London!
어서 런던으로 가
Really?
정말?
문 앞에 나타나 놀라게 해줘
싸우지도 않고 포기하지 마
Surprise her.
Don't let her go without a fight.
All right. I'm going to do it.
알았어
좋아, 해볼게
그래
I'm going to London,
and I'll fight for her.
런던으로 날아가
싸워 이길 거야
좋아, 행운을 빌게
Okay. Good luck!
로스! 공항에 가면 지난번에
그 초콜릿 하나 더 사다줄래?
Can you pick me up one
of those Toblerone bars at the airport?
I did it!
I figured out a way to make money.
드디어 돈 벌
방법이 생각났어
프랭크하고 같이
안마시술소를 여는 거야
I'll open a massage place.
Frank will help me.
동생 스케줄에 맞추면 학교도
계속 다닐 수 있지? 룰루랄라!
We'll work it around his schedule,
so he doesn't have to quit school.
But how can you afford it?
괜찮은 생각인데
무슨 돈으로?
We were walking down the street,
and we saw your van.
너희가 출장요리사업에
쓰려던 밴을 봤거든
- 그 순간...
- 내가 얘기할 거얏!
-And we realized
-I'm telling it!
사람들에겐 차도 필요하지만
가끔은 마사지도 필요하니까
People need transportation,
and they need massages to relax.
We can combine the two.
I give massages and Frank drives.
이 두 개를 결합하는 거야
난 마사지, 프랭크는 운전
I'll bolt a table in the van,
and you know what I've got?
밴 뒤에 테이블을 달면
뭐가 되는지 알아?
A place that no one
will get out of alive?
아무도 살아 나오지
못하는 차?
Think about it. It's a taxi that
people take when they need to relax.
아냐, 잘 생각해봐
피로를 풀고 싶을 때 타는 택시
It's a Relaxi-Taxi!
피로회복 택시!
The name was my favorite part!
제일 중요한 걸 가로채?
-I came up with it.
-You did not!
- 내가 생각해냈잖아
- 네가 언제!
아냐
You came up with Relaxi-Cab.
That's not good.
넌 '원기충전 택시'라고 했지
그건 영 아냐
- 여보세요
- 나야
세상에
Oh, my god! Are you in England?
Was Emily surprised?
오빠 지금 영국이야?
에밀리가 반가워하지?
아니, 집에 없더라
밤새 안 들어왔어
No, she hasn't come home yet.
She hasn't been home all night.
She must be with the other guy.
그 녀석하고 있는 게 분명한데
I'm the stupid moron
who spent the night here.
나만 빈집 앞에서 밤을
꼴딱 새며 궁상을 떨었잖아
-What was that?
-I just put my fist through another wall.
무슨 소리야?
방금 벽 하나 더 뚫었다
애들한테 얘기해라
Tell the guys.
When is the next flight out?
- 다음 비행기는 언제야?
- 네 시간 후에
About four hours.
Stay there for a while.
If she doesn't show up, come home.
조금만 더 기다려보고
그때도 안 나타나면 돌아와
There's a girl at the restaurant
that would be perfect for you.
참, 오빠한테 딱 맞는
식당여급을 발견했어
Tell him about Relaxi-Taxi.
피로회복 택시 얘기도 해
Ask him if he likes it
better than Relaxi-Cab.
원기충전 택시보다
나은지 물어보고
It's not Relaxi-Cab.
It's Relaxi-Cab. Like Taxi-Cab.
원기충전이 아니라 원기충천!
사기충천! 할 때처럼
That is better.
그건 괜찮네
Do you have any 8's?
- 혹시 8 있어?
- 아니
No.
Are we in London?
여기 런던이냐?
Why are you here?
You can't be here.
웬일이에요
여기 있으면 안 되는데
I've come to talk to Ross.
로스한테 할말이 있어서
허걱...
What?
왜요?
Nothing.
그냥 뭐, 아니에요
I was going to call him
전화하려고 했지만...
사랑 고백하러 왔군요
그럴 줄 알았어!
You came to tell him you love him.
I knew it!
I was right!
I'm right, right?
내 말이 맞지?
맞죠? 그쵸?
I'd rather talk to him.
직접 얘기하고 싶네요
집에 가봤더니 없더라구요
만나서 얘기하고 싶은데...
I've been to his apartment
and he's not there.
I need to talk to him.
Do you know where he is?
지금 어디 있죠?
Ross, are you there?
로스, 거기 있어?
Ross, I don't know if you hear this,
but I'll talk anyway.
자기가 이걸 들을 수 있는지
모르겠지만 어쨌든 말할게
I'm in the States
with your sister and friends.
여기 미국이야
자기 친구들이랑 있어
It's all over with Colin.
컬린과는 완전히 끝났어
자기한테 할말이
있어서 왔는데... 네?
I came here to tell you that
and to tell you
Yes, Joey, you can have
all the chocolate you want.
그래요, 조이
초콜릿은 다 먹어도 돼요
I came here to tell you
that I love you.
이 말을 하려고 왔어
자기를 사랑해
I love you too!
나도 사랑해!
I'll call you right now
from the phone booth.
당장 공중전화로 달려갈게!
내 말 안 들리지?
You can't hear me.
I wish I knew if you'd heard me.
이거 자기가 들은 게 아니라면
동네사람들한테 웃음거리만 돼
I suppose I've given
my neighbors a good laugh.
Mrs. Newman, if you're listening,
bugger off. None of your business.
뉴먼 부인, 남의 사생활에
신경 끊고 저리 가주세요
There's not much chance
you did hear that.
내 얘기 못 들었겠지?
다른 전화가 왔네
There's the call waiting...
...so I should go.
그럼 끊을게
이런...
Oh, well.
여보세요?
나야
Ross, I love you.
로스, 사랑해
고마워
Thank you.
- 나 왔어
- 그래
I was just at the bank.
There was this really hot teller...
방금 은행에 가서
빠방한 여직원을 봤는데
...and she didn't ask me
to do it with her in the vault.
날 금고로 안 데려가더라?
Same thing happened to me.
나도 똑같은 일을 당했어
Pizza delivery girl comes over,
gives me the pizza and leaves!
여자 피자배달원이 왔는데
피자 값만 받고 그냥 가잖아
No "Nice apartment,
bet the bedrooms are huge"?
이 집 침대 크냐고
물어보지도 않고?
Nothing!
아무 말도 없었다니까
You know what?
We have to turn off the porn.
아무래도 이젠
포르노 꺼야겠다
I think you're right.
옳으신 말씀
Ready?
준비됐냐?
하나, 둘, 셋
One, two, three.
그거 괜찮다
That's kind of nice.
- 마음이 편안해
- 그래
That's kind of a relief.
You want to see
if we still have it?
- 아직 나오나 볼까?
- 그래
-Free porn!
-We have free porn!
- 공짜 포르노다!
- 아자! 만세!
There's one, two and three.
보세요, 하나
둘, 그리고 셋
-Oh, my God.
-That's so beautiful.
- 세상에...
- 눈물난다
-Oh, man.
-I can't believe it.
- 믿어지지 않아요
- 그렇죠?
I know.
I like the middle one the best.
중간에 있는 녀석이 제일 좋아
Don't worry,
I won't let the other two know.
걱정 마, 나머지 둘한테
알려준 거니까